[{"answer": "At least your nightmare is only a dream. What about what happened to my friend", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "You never heard of the famous Dr. my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Fensterwald. my friend. It sounds familiar but... They sure come out of the woodwork when you get famous, my friend. Put him through", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "that place, I'm my friend. I represent the that place. I can offer you a forty percent discount on our toothpicks plus a very attractive selection of toothpick holders if..", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Elementary school?  I thought you were Overton Cafeteria", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " This is my friend. I'm a patient of Dr. my friend's. I need to talk to him. Urgently", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Ah", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Is this a bad time", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh no, they told you? I fibbed a little but... Don't be mad.  Oh..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "How do you know it's a death fixation? Maybe I'm in mourning for my lost childhood", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What do you mean by asking", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Excellent. But what I can do", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Exactly. What I can do is this", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend said you're not treating him here", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "So if you're not treating him while he's here, then he's not a patient while he's here, is he? And I have the right to see him", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Look, I said I was wrong now I'd like to forget it. I'd like you all to accept my apology", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What about my friend?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I think we should invite him for dinner", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Dinner", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh. Sorry, my friend. Would you pass the salt", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'm sorry. You said in your office that I could call you my friend", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "And don't call me my friend", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "That was in my office. In my home you will call me Dr. my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Of course you are", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Have you seen my new toothbrush", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well it should be but it's not", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend, it's not the interview", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No, Siggy. Yes, my friend! Who else", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Sure. Are you kidding", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Halcyon? Seconal", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I'll be quiet", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Thank you", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Oh, sorry. This is my wife, er, my friend. My daughter my friend, and my son..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Whose side are you on?", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "I'm relaxed", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " my friend's... unavailable right now. Can... I take a message", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": " that place canceling order... Any message why", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " that place canceling order... Any message why", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": " Not priority... right now.  Why", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Son of a bitch", "docId": "What-About-Bob-.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Ass wipe of the universe", "qsentId": 48}]